meetyourfriends.com 2010-08-06

# Read Privacy Policy for safe online personals and chatting

We treat your privacy as our number one priority and make every effort to safeguard your personal information. This Privacy Policy has been developed to keep your information secure while using MeetYourFriends. Please take time to read and understand our Privacy Policy.

## Summary of Privacy Policy

The main points of this Privacy Policy are:

  * It is only necessary to submit the minimum user information to join MeetYourFriends.
  * You choose which personal information to share with the MeetYourFriends community.
  * Your personal information will not be sold or rented out to any third party.
  * MeetYourFriends does not spam.
  * Only adults aged 18 and over may use the services of MeetYourFriends.
  * You can request that your membership profile be deactivated at any time.
  * By joining up to MeetYourFriends, you agree to this Privacy Policy, otherwise you should not use the site.

## Table of Contents

MeetYourFriends and Collection of Information

When you register to use the MeetYourFriends network we collect certain information to verify your identity and administer your account. We only require basic information from you to set up a personal profile on MeetYourFriends. This includes personal information you submit such as your name, date of birth, sex and email address. However, at a later stage you may wish to include additional information on your personal profile or in the messages you send to other users. This information is your responsibility and may include hobbies, education, religious beliefs, ethnic origin and family status. Please ensure that this information does not break our Terms of Use.

Automatic Information and Cookies

MeetYourFriends tracks and collects information from your computer which is sent automatically when you use our service. This data includes your IP address, browser type and cookies. We may also gather information on your navigation habits of MeetYourFriends such as the features you use. This information is collected for the purposes of analysis and security and is used to improve your online experience. In particular, we analyze the information regarding geographic location to establish the number of international and local personals.

Cookies are common text files downloaded onto your computer via your browser when you visit a website. Like most websites, MeetYourFriends uses cookies to analyze user traffic and retrieve login information to make it easier for you to regularly use the website. If you switch off cookies then you may have problems using MeetYourFriends.

Use and Disclosure of Information

Your personal information will not be sold or rented out to any third party. The personal information we gather from you is used in a number of ways. Selected information forms the basis of your personal profile that is displayed to other members of MeetYourFriends in a person search. We will make the means available to other users who would like to contact you.

Your personal information will be used to carry out internal duties including analysis of site usage, improvements to our website layout and artwork, and fulfillment of our obligations regarding applicable law. If there is a crime committed or suspicion of a crime committed we may have to supply your online communications and other information in response to the relevant legal process (such as a search warrant, court order or subpoena). In this instance, it may not be possible to inform you of this course of action.

We will use your email address to get in touch about important services and security information. It is possible for you to opt in or out of these messages via your personal profile settings. This information may also be evaluated to provide advertising and promotions that are tailored to your specific preferences. We believe this is fair usage of your personal information and helps keep you informed and provides a better service.

Personal information may also be used to troubleshoot problems, resolve disputes and implement our Terms of Use.

We reserve the right to transfer your personal profile in the event of a change of ownership of MeetYourFriends, including acquisitions and mergers. If this Privacy Policy changes as a result, we will notify you of the amendments.

Children and Age of Use Policy

Minors and those under the age of 18 are not eligible to use MeetYourFriends and must not try to register personal details with MeetYourFriends. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18 or allow them to register. By using the Website, you represent and warrant that you have the right, authority, and capacity to enter into the Terms of Use and abide by all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you have reason to believe this policy has been contravened, please [Contact Us](mailto:support@meetyourfriends.com) immediately and we will delete the offending personal profile.

Your Responsibility to Other Users

MeetYourFriends is for the personal use of individual Members only and may not be used in connection with any commercial endeavors. It is your responsibility when using MeetYourFriends to treat other users in an appropriate and honorable manner. You may not use the information of other users (private or otherwise) for spam, commercial purposes, or to make unlawful threats and harassments. We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of those who violate the Terms of Use and misuse the information of others.

Security and Confidentiality

MeetYourFriends actively implements and updates security measures to protect and prevent the exploitation, alteration and loss of all information on the website, including your personal information. MeetYourFriends incorporates industry standard techniques (such as firewalls) to protect the safety of your personal information and our technicians make every effort to prevent loss or disclosure of your personal details.

We request that you do not share your username and password with any third parties in public forums, chat rooms, blogs or any other online or offline area. If your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password in Account Settings.

Reviewing, Deleting and Changing Your Profile

You have the control to review, correct and change your personal profile at any time in the settings panel. Information you may change includes your contact email address, your profile and photographs, your location and your password. If you would like to remove your personal profile, please [Contact Us](mailto:support@meetyourfriends.com) and we will ensure that your account is cancelled. We welcome any feedback you may have.

Inactivity

If you have been inactive on MeetYourFriends for over 45 days we reserve the right to deactivate your personal profile as part of our data cleansing practices.

Updates to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Any changes to our Privacy Policy or email practices will be posted here and in other areas deemed necessary and appropriate. If we make substantial changes to our Privacy Policy, we will contact you via email or place a notice on our homepage.

The last update to this Privacy Policy was on 1st May 2010.
